<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Malbolge</title>
    <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Malbolge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:08:57 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>001</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:08:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story1/</guid>
      <description>John was an intrepid and ambitious young man at the outset of his 20&amp;rsquo;s. His head was filled with ideas that had been motivated greatly by the words of the famous thinkers like Niels Bohr and Albert Einstein, who both engaged in a passionate disagreement as to indeterminacy in quantum mechanics. As he grew older, the thought of mortality began to haunt him; it made his skin crawl, so he sought solace in the warmth of the scientific world where he could observe and admire the universe and its many marvels and intricacies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:08:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story2/</guid>
      <description>My name is Septimus and I was born on a particularly starless night. Progeny of a family of literary geniuses and musicians, I sought refuge in poetry as a means of escape. As I grew, the way the white paper would be filled with the colors of my unending musings, I grew to love the art of poetry and writing. It was then I went to college, my colleagues and I, having high expectations of ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:08:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/story3/</guid>
      <description>Once there lived a mother with a child, Whose name be unknown yet vitally mild, The innocence of the child was stellar, His beautiful smile brought beauty to her.
Every morning was a joy of her living, Seeing joy and mirth his smile was giving, But fate had something else to give, Unknown to the mother, his life to relive.
When the child grew, his mind was spun, Finding himself amongst the capitalistic pun, Was it a sin or a life just set?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chadgpt</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/chadgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:08:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/chadgpt/chadgpt/</guid>
      <description>Chatgpt is a natural language processing chatbot that is quite nifty. Here are a few works that I made using chadgpt. Most works of chatgpt may come off as very vague or &amp;ldquo;non-human&amp;rdquo;, but those results are the consequence of poor prompts. One has to provide some degree of context and other paramters that&amp;rsquo;d let the nlp bot give you what you want. For example, if I wanted Chatgpt to generate a poem in Chaucer&amp;rsquo;s English or in a style that reflects Dostoevesky&amp;rsquo;s, I should specify so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monologue</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/monologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 22:22:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/monologue/</guid>
      <description>What is the purpose of this website? Like my life, this website lacks purpose. It simply exists because I will for it to exist. I exist. I was brought into existence, against my will. I continue to exist with my will. I will exist till the day I lose my will. Somewhere out there, there is someone who answers to my name. I cannot say where you&amp;rsquo;d be able to find me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/langinfur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 21:37:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/langinfur/</guid>
      <description>The words I use, intentionally or unintentionally, have their own meanings, which cease to exist when I place them with other words. Does the meaning of a sentence so formed have the same meaning as the summation of the individual meanings of its constituent words? All sentences can have multiple meanings when read by multiple people. Where exactly does my intention get lost in a sentence and from where do personal inferences begin?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intoxicant</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/intoxicant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 23:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/intoxicant/</guid>
      <description>You were the puff I couldn&amp;rsquo;t exhale.
Even when my alveoli threatened to burn
and my breathing became fatally frail,
about you, I remained foolishly stubborn.
No sun could light my world.
No thunder could instill fear.
And then , emotions unfurled,
when, to you, I happened near.
Melody and noise was the same.
I was blind to poetry&amp;rsquo;s glow.
And then you lit in me a flame.
I submitted to the ethereal flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/death/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 23:00:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/death/</guid>
      <description>I want to die
When I think of death, I hear silence. Unlike the rough bustle of the living, this silence carriers tenderness. Unlike the blinding lights of mankind, death arrives with cool darkness. When I think of death, I remember the janitors from my school cleaning the blackboards fastidiously with maladorous grey-green rag clothes. Unlike a duster, the rag cloth would clean it black, in a manner that&amp;rsquo;d quench my visual thirst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:37:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/personal/</guid>
      <description>Random Materials
| 9.0Mb | Mathematical Methods in Linguistics | 4.6Mb | Speech and Language Processing | 14.0Mb| Logic and Methods of Formal Reasoning | 24.0Mb| RBook | 9.1Mb | Dignified Dying | 6.8Mb | Dante&amp;rsquo;s Inferno | 1.1Mb | Wallpaper Dotfiles
|822M| DOTS </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumables: Ranked</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/cr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:37:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/cr/</guid>
      <description>Anime Secret Experiments Lain Ergo Proxy Stein&amp;rsquo;s Gate Cowboy Bepop Berserk Erased/ Boku Dake Ga Inai Machi Operating Systems Void Linux Alpine Linux Artix Linux Free BSD YT Channels Mental Outlaw Tom Scott Luke Smith Louis Rossman CTT Veritasium Secession Studios Aperture OverSimplified </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lore</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/lore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:50:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/lore/</guid>
      <description>Mine is a story that&amp;rsquo;d leave readers feeling nothing. It is simply a story that has its fair share of lunacy and sanity. As you pore through this , instead of doing whatever it is that you ought to be doing, you might feel intrigued as to why this page exists or you might feel a tinge of regret for chancing upon this abysmal site.
Since I am too lazy to rewrite my lore to fit my current persona, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to read about my life from the words of the person I was, 3-4 months ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Description</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:38:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/description/</guid>
      <description>Χαιρετίσματα weary traveller!
This is , if you haven&amp;rsquo;t figured it out yet, my personal website. Here, I unleash my lunacy, anger and fears and let them masquerade as creativity and talent. The previous sentence, I am well aware, is not accurate. But, I have lost the human ability to articulate sentences properly. Chomsky boi and his cohorts believe that language is something that is ingrained in all of our genes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Index to all my writeups</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:38:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you can find links to my various writeups. Please send your criticism via email to this address
Death |14.02.2023| Language: An Infuriating Gestalten |01.02.2023| Intoxicant |21.01.2023| </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Index to all my writeups</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/bruh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:38:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/bruh/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you can find links to my various writeups. Please send your criticism via email to this address
Death |14.02.2023| Language: An Infuriating Gestalten |01.02.2023| Intoxicant |21.01.2023| </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liminal Space</title>
      <link>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:38:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewaywardlaureate.github.io/bruh/ls/</guid>
      <description>Welcome,oh adventurer, to this place that exists between what is going to happen and what has happened. It has no tethers with the present, the past and the future. It exists at the threshold. Somewhere where something inexplicable occurs. Remain where you are. Savour this freedom from time. No future to worry about, no past to cry over and no present spent in confusion.
Embrace this change.
though it is strange</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
